LIDIA SAPINSKA .COM

PROFILE

Facts before opinions - Dialog before the conclusion. UX Professional, passionate fairytale illustrator & sex workers rights supporter. Emphatic interviewer and a great entity to discuss the dark matter of life with. Feminist, activist and visual artist.

I truly belive in equity and equality between people. Using huge part of my brain capacity to make sure that "we are doing things right" is one of my main attributes. I value honesty, friendship and communication, and I will always fight for people and good ideas as valorously as a true Klingon.

I believe that research & communication makes a perfect combination for an endless process of improving things. So take my hand and let's find the new things to improve!



EXPERIENCE

USER RESEARCHER & UX PROFFESIONAL | January 2018 - Present METRO GROUP (METRO, METRONOM, METRO DIGITAL) Düsseldorf, Berlin

Researched & designed product: https://produkte.metro.de/shop

UX DESIGNER | July 2017 - August 2018 IQ.PL Online

Researched & designed product: lq.pi.www

ART DIRECTOR + UX DESIGNER | January 2017 - August 2017 JET EVENTS Warsaw

Event Marketing Agency

- designing and wireframing UI/UX for event apps
- designing landing pages, event web sites

JUNIOR ART DIRECTOR | March 2016 - January 2017 **VACALOCA Warsaw**

Social Media Agency

- designing and wireframing
- designing landing pages, web sites and online games
- creating event 'big ideas' and concepts

SENIOR DESIGNER + UX/UI DESIGNER | August 2015 - April 2017 BELIANIi.ch Szczecin

Researched & designed products: www.beliani.ch www.whatdajob.com (project discontinued)

SKILLS

User Research, User Interviews, High People Skills Concept Design, Information Architecture, Interaction Design, Complex User Flows, Visual Design

TOOLS

Sketch, Axure, Adobe Creative Suite, InVision, Abstract, Zeplin, Basic HTML & CSS, Miro, JIRA,

EDUCATION

ACADEMY OF ART Szczecin, Poland | 2010-2015 Bachelor of Arts Master of Arts

ACADEMY OF FINE ARTS Gdansk, Poland | 2008 - 2011 Bachelor of Arts

LANGUAGES

Enalish **FLUENT** Polish **NATIVE** Russian NATIVE German **BASIC**

INTERESTS

Last century eastern-european science fiction literature memes & memetics, evolution. slavic herbs, social economics, russian and northern european fairytales, art, painting (...and more!)

CONTACT

hetane@gmail.com (0048) 510537901

LINKS

www.lidiasapinska.com www.linkedin.com/in/caryca www.behance.net/caryca